let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What are the primary colors in a program? ",
        answer: "A. red, green, blue",
        options: [
            "A. red, green, blue",
            "B. white, black, brown",
            "C. gray, charcoal, purple",  
            "D. maroon, olive, indigo",  
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What number is hexadecimal base?", 
        answer: "A. 16", 
        options: [
            "A. 16",
            "B. 17", 
            "C. 18",
            "D. 19"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "How many CSS colors are there?",
        answer: "C. 140",
        options: [
            "A. 50", 
            "B. 60", 
            "C. 140", 
            "D. 200" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is a hex code used for?",
        answer: "D. identifying colors",
        options: [
            "A. numbering a base",
            "B. calling a color in a program",
            "C. identifying a number in program",
            "D. identifying colors"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Hexadecimal is a 6 digit representation of a color. What is the first two digits?",
        answer: "A. (RR)",
        options: [
            "A. (RR)", 
            "B. (AA)", 
            "C. (BB)", 
            "D. (CC)" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is the syntax of hex code? ",
        answer: "B. #RRGGBB",
        options: [
            "A. #RGB", 
            "B. #RRGGBB", 
            "C. #rgb(rrr%,ggg,bbb)", 
            "D. #rgb(rrr,ggg,bbb)", 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the Hexadecimal notation of color red?",
        answer: "C. #FF0000",
        options: [
            "A. #000000", 
            "B. #00FF00", 
            "C. #FF0000", 
            "D. #0000FF" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "CSS uses color values to specify what? ",
        answer: "A. color",
        options: [
            "A. color",
            "B. the arrangement of words",
            "C. a set of rules",
            "D. a hexadecimal notation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the hexadecimal notation of color white?",
        answer: "B. #FFFFFF",
        options: [
            "A. #FFF",
            "B. #FFFFFF",
            "C. #FFFF",
            "D. #FFFFF"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Each hexadecimal code will be preceded by a pound or __ sign? ",
        answer: "D. hash",
        options: [
            "A. tag", 
            "B. notation", 
            "C. number", 
            "D. hash"            

        ]
    },
]